Cioni, Peter J. Labor Agreement Collection 5916
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I. COMPANY PUBLICATIONS & DOCUMENTS
  - Sub-Series A. AGREEMENTS
    - Kelsey-Hayes Wheel Company and UAW, Local 670, 1947-1951; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Item 1: Kelsey-Hayes Wheel Company and UAW, Local 670, 1947-1948; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 7)
        4/26/47 - 4/25/48.
      - Item 2: Kelsey-Hayes Wheel Company and UAW, Local 670, 1949-1951; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 7)
        6/23/49 - 6/22/51.
    - Lefere Forge & Machine Co. and UAW, Local 504, 1950-1955; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 8)
      11/6/50 - 11/6/55
    - Liftow, Inc. and IAM, Elm Lodge 420, 1962-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 9)
      7/30/62 - 8/2/64
    - Lynchburg Foundry Company, Lynchburg Plant and USA, Local 2556, 1973-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Item 1: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Lynchburg Plant and USA, Local 2556, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
        5/1/73 - 4/30/76.
      - Item 2: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Archer Creek Plant and USA, Local 8270, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
        7/15/74 - 11/1/76.
      - Item 3: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Lynchburg Plant and USA, Local 2556., 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
        5/1/76 - 4/30/79.
      - Item 4: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Lynchburg Plant and USA, Local 2556., 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Item 5: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Radford Plant and USA, Local 2969, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Item 6: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Archer Creek Plant and USA, Local 8270, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
        11/1/76 - 11/2/79.
      - Item 7: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Lynchburg Plant and USA, Local 2556, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
        7/1/79 - 4/30/82.
      - Item 8: Lynchburg Foundry Company, Lynchburg Plant and USA, Local 2556, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Michigan Bell Telephone Co, 1948-1952; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Item 1: Michigan Bell Telephone Co. vs Communications Workers of America, Michigan Division 43, 1948-1949; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 11)
        12/30/48 - 12/30/49.
      - Item 2: Michigan Bell Telephone Co. vs Communications Workers of America, Michigan Division 15, 1950-1952; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 11)
        11/30/50 - 2/15/52.
    - Motor Wheel Corporation and UAW, Local 724, 1956-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 12)
      2/15/56 - 10/15/58
    - Muskegon Motor Specialties Company and UAW, Local 953, 1972-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 13)
      9/1/72 - 9/1/75.
    - National Automotive Fibres, Inc. and Textile Workers Union of America (TWA)., 1955-1957; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 14)
      3/1/55 - 3/1/57
    - Neelon Casting Ltd. and USA, Local 6363, 1983-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 15)
      9/1/83 - 8/31/85
    - Newman Foundry Company, Inc. and IMAW, Local 262, 1975-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Item 1: Newman Foundry Company, Inc. and IMAW, Local 262, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 16)
        5/1/75 - 4/30/78.
      - Item 2: Newman Foundry Company, Inc. and IMAW, Local 262, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 16)
        5/1/75 - 4/30/78. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Newman Foundry Company, Inc. and IMAW, Local 262, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 16)
        5/1/78 - 4/30/81.
    - Noblesville Casting Inc. vs UAW, Local 1571, 1986-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 17)
      11//5/86 - 11/20/87
    - Oliver Corporation, Battle Creek Plant No. 1 and UAW, Local 873, 1955-1958; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 18)
      12/19/55 - 12/1/58.
    - One Sunday Visitor, Inc. of Huntington, Indiana and Huntington Printing Pressmen' Union, Local 411, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 19)
      7/1/74 - 6/30/77.
    - Packard Motor Car Company and UAW, Local 190, 1946-1947; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 20)
      6/7/46 -6/7/47
    - Pangborn Division of the Carborundum Company and UAW, Local 842., 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 21)
      7/8/74 - 3/3/77.
    - RCA Corporation and IBEW, Local 1424, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 22)
      12/1/73 - 12/1/76
    - Sheet Aluminum Corporation and UAW, Local 559, 1950-1952; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 23)
      8/1/50 - 8/1/52
    - Sundstrand Corporation and UAW, Local 592, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 24)
      5/17/71 - 5/19/74
    - Tokheim Corporation and UAW, Local 1539, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 25)
      1/6/69 - 1/5/72.
    - Walker Manufacturing Company vs, UAW, Local Unions 85 and 660, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 26)
      2/1/74 - 2/28/77.
    - Warner Gear Division, Borg-Warner Corp. and UAW, Local 287, 1961-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Item 1: Warner Gear Division, Borg-Warner Corp. and UAW, Local 287, 1961-1964; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 27)
        11/6/61 - 10/14/64.
      - Item 2: Warner Gear Division, Borg-Warner Corp. and UAW, Local 287, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 27)
        12/7/64 - 10/14/67.
      - Item 3: Warner Gear Division, Borg-Warner Corp. and UAW, Local 287, 1968-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 27)
        1/15/68 - 11/1/70.
      - Item 4: Warner Gear Division, Borg-Warner Corp. and UAW, Local 287, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 27)
        3/7/77-2/8/80.
    - Willys-Overland Motors, Inc. and UAW, Local 12, 1946-1947; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 3, Folder 28)
      3/1/46 - 8/1/47
  - Sub-Series B. PUBLICATIONS
    - Canadian Clark, Ltd., St. Thomas, Ontario. Labor Policy Manual & Handbook for Employees, Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 1)
      32p
    - Clark Equipment Company, 1961-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Item 1: Apprentice Standards, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Sponsored the Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan & Allied Industrial Workers of America. Revised May 1, 1971.
      - Item 2: Apprentice Standards, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Sponsored the Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan & Allied Industrial Workers of America. Revised May 1, 1971. Copy 2.
      - Item 3: Group Health and Accident Insurance Plan, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Negotiated by Local 623, UAW-AFL with Clark Equipment Company, Transmission Division. nd.
      - Item 4: Transmission Division, Jackson, Michigan. Group Insurance Plan. Hourly Paid Employees, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        no date.
      - Item 5: Handbook for Employees, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Revised December 1965. Second Printing, February, 1973.
      - Item 6: Handbook for Employees, 1965; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Revised December 1965. Second Printing, February, 1973. Copy 2.
      - Item 7: Instructions for Employees to Account for Moving and Relocation Expenses, 1978; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        15- Sep-78.
      - Item 8: A Statement on Supervisory Conduct During a Union Campaign for Recognition and a Guide to Basic Principles of Supervision, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Item 9: A Statement Regarding Supervisory Conduct When Work Stoppages or Slow-Downs Occur, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Revised April 1961.
      - Item 10: A Statement Regarding Supervisory Conduct When Work Stoppages or Slow-Downs Occur, 1961; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        Revised April 1961. Copy 2.
      - Item 11: Summary Plan Description. Group Insurance Plan. Jackson Hourly Employees, Plan no.540., 1976; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        May-76.
      - Item 12: Summary Plan Description. Pension Plan. Jackson Hourly Employees, Plan no.003., 1976; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Item 13: Summary Plan Description. Pension Plan. Jackson Hourly Employees, Plan no.003., 1976; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        May-76. Copy 2.
      - Item 14: Summary Plan Description. Pension Plan. Jackson Hourly Employees, Plan no.509., 1976; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Item 15: Two's Company Three's A Crowd: A Guide to Maintaining Non-Union Status and Combating Union Organization Attempts, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Item 16: Two's Company Three's A Crowd: A Guide to Maintaining Non-Union Status and Combating Union Organization Attempts, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 2)
        no date. Copy 2.
    - Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1956-1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Item 1: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1956; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1956.
      - Item 2: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1957; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        February 4, 1957.
      - Item 3: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1959; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        November 1, 1959.
      - Item 4: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1960; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        November 7. 1960.
      - Item 5: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        March 5, 1962.
      - Item 6: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        March 5, 1962. Copy 2.
      - Item 7: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        March 26, 1962.
      - Item 8: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1962; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        August 1, 1962.
      - Item 9: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        March 4, 1963.
      - Item 10: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        March 4, 1963. Copy 2.
      - Item 11: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1964; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        March 2, 1964.
      - Item 12: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        June 6, 1966.
      - Item 13: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1966; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        June 6, 1966. Copy 2.
      - Item 14: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        June 5, 1967.
      - Item 15: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1967; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        June 5, 1967. Copy 2.
      - Item 16: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1969; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 5, 1969.
      - Item 17: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1972; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1972.
      - Item 18: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1973; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 7, 1973.
      - Item 19: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1974; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1974.
      - Item 20: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1974; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1974. Copy 2.
      - Item 21: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1975; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 5, 1975.
      - Item 22: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1975; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 5, 1975. Copy 2.
      - Item 23: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1976; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 3, 1976.
      - Item 24: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1976; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 3, 1976. Copy 2.
      - Item 25: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1977; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1977.
      - Item 26: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1977; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1977. Copy 2.
      - Item 27: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1978; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1978.
      - Item 28: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1978; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1978. Copy 2.
      - Item 29: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1978; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1978. Copy 3.
      - Item 30: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1979; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 7, 1979.
      - Item 31: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1979; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 7, 1979. Copy 2.
      - Item 32: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1980; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 1, 1980.
      - Item 33: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 3, 1982.
      - Item 34: Clark Equipment Company. Wage and Classification Schedule for Production, Maintenance and Tool Divisions, 1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 3)
        May 3, 1982. Copy 2.
    - Borg-Warner. Warner Gear Division. Insurance, 1968-1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Item 1: Borg-Warner. Warner Gear Division. Certificate of Insurance, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
        Connecticut General Life Insurance Company, February 1971 edition.
      - Item 2: Borg-Warner. Warner Gear Division. Group Insurance Plan, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Item 3: Borg-Warner. Warner Gear Division. Group Insurance Program, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Item 4: Borg-Warner. Warner Gear Division. Group Insurance Program for Office and Supervisory Employees, 1968-1970; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 4)
        October 1, 1968 - January 1, 1970.
    - International Harvester Company. Fort Wayne Plant. Planning Your Future: A Pre-Retirement Planning Guide, 1970; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Jun-70
    - Lunkenheimer Company, Cincinnati, Ohio. Factory Rules and Regulations, 1946; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 6)
      17-Apr- 46
- Series II. GENERAL POLITICS
  - Sub-Series A. General - Political
    - General political material - flyers, pamphlets, 1925-1980; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series B. Civil Rights
    - Pamphlet. On the Battlefield: Cario, Illinois, 1970; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Prepared by the Concerned Community Coalition of Bloomington-Normal and Community for Social Action. 36 pp
  - Sub-Series C. Nixon-McGovern Presidential Election
    - Flyers, cartoon, bumper sticker, memo from George McGovern, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series D. Viet Nam War
    - Flyers, 1971; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Series III. MONOGRAPHS
  - Gardiner, Glen. How To Handle Grievances, 1952; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Mount Vernon, NY, Elliott Service Company, 1952. 52 pp.
  - Jackson Community College. Related Trade Instruction for Apprentices Employees in Training Journey and Up-Graders, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 12)
    79 p. nd.
  - Modern Language Association of America. The MLA Style Sheet, 1970; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Second edition. 1970. 48 pp
  - Sellers, Charles. The Coming of the War, 1917, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 14)
    The Berkeley Series in American History. Chicago, Rand McNally & Company, 1963. 55 pp.
  - Sellers, Charles. The Issue of Federal Regulation in the Progressive Era, 1963; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 15)
    The Berkeley Series in American History. Chicago, Rand McNally & Company, 1963. 58 pp
- Series IV. NATIONAL RIGHT TO WORK COMMITTEE
  - Unfinished manuscript (Chapter 5), 1973; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 16)
    21 pages. nd; flyers; news release; Right to Work Profiles, 12 pp. pamphlet, May 1973
- Series V. SCHOLARLY PUBLICATION
  - Daffara, John C. The Social Rational Behind the Taft-Hartley Act of 1947, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 17)
    18pp
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Atlanta. Essays on Southern Economic Growth, 1960-1961; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 18)
    (Selected articles from the Monthly Review), 1960-61. May 1961. 31 pp
  - Management's Objectives in Industrial Relations, 1950; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 19)
    . An Address by W.J. Reilly, Manager, Labor Relations, International Harvester Company. Based on Remarks Made Before The Richmond Works' Management Organization. January 17, 1950. 9 pp.
  - McKersie, Robert B. and William W. Shropshire, Jr. Avoiding Written Grievances: A Successful Program.., 1962; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Reprinted from the Journal of Business of the University of Chicago, 1962. pp.135 - 152
  - Position Papers of the United Automobile Workers Union, 1976 (mainly as presented to General Motors Corp.) And the Initial Auto Company Replies., Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 21)
    Reprinted from the original Auto Union and company position papers by Trends Publishing Co., Southfield, MI. 104 pp.
  - Schatzki, George. Majority Rule, Exclusive Representation, and the Interests of Individual Workers: Should Exclusivity Be Abolished, 1975; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Reprinted from University of Pennsylvania Law Review, Philadelphia, PA., Vol. 123, No. 4, April 1975. pp. 897-938
  - Wyman, Mark. Industrial Revolution in the West: Hard-Rock Miners and the New Technology, 1974; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Reprinted from The Western Historical Quarterly, Vol. V, No. 1, January 1974. pp. 39-57
- Series VI. UNION (ANTI) PROPAGANDA
  - Flyers, brochures, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Series VII. UNION MEMORABILIA
  - Bumper stickers, election material, etc., Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Series VIII. UNION PAMPHLETS
  - Sub-Series A. BYLAWS
    - AIW, U.S.A., and UAW By-Laws, 1969-1981; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Item 1: AIW, Local 623, 1980; Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
        Adopted October 24, 1980.
      - Item 2: AIW, Local 623, 1971; Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
        Adopted December 11, 1971.
      - Item 3: UAW, Local 504, Lefere Forge & Machine Co., Jackson, Michigan, Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Item 4: USA, By-laws for Local Unions, 1969; Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
        April 1969..November 1981.
      - Item 5: USA, By-laws for Local Unions (Including supplementary provisions for Amalgamated Local Unions), 1981; Constitutions and By- Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
        November 1981.
      - Item 6: USA, By-laws for Local Unions (Including supplementary provisions for Amalgamated Local Unions), 1981; Constitutions and By- Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
        November 1981. Copy 2.
      - Item 7: USA, District 30, By-laws for Welfare and Education Fund, 1982; Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 26)
        May 1982.
  - Sub-Series B. UNION PAMPHLETS, BROCHURES, MISCELLANEOUS PUBLICATIONS
    - AIW, AFL-CIO. Pamphlets, 1978-1983; Constitutions and By-Laws (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Item 1: Manual for Stewards and Committeemen: A Guide to Leadership, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 27)
        38 pp. nd.
      - Item 2: Your Company is Cordially Invited to Exhibit at the forthcoming AFL-CIO Union-Industrial Show, 1983; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 27)
        March 25-30, 1983.
      - Item 3: Local 623 Honor Award for Good Citizenship, 1982; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 27)
        October 29, 1982.
      - Item 4: To the Management of Clark Equipment Company, 1978; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 27)
        November 22, 1978. Letter of thanks for "Open House" and "Family Day".
    - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations. Pamphlets, 1980-1984; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Item 1: How to Run a Union Meeting, 1980; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
        64 pp.
      - Item 2: Department of Economic Research. Reaganomics: A Profile of Failure., 1984; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
        May 1984. 17 pp.
      - Item 3: 1983 AFL-CIO Union-Industries Show, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Item 4: Register Vote, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Item 5: H.R.8410 and S.1883 Labor Law Reform, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Item 6: Back Up Your Ballot with Your Bucks, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Item 7: Fight for My Union? Damn Right I Would!, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - UAW. Pamphlets, 1973-1977; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Item 1: Ammunition, 1973; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
        Vol. 14, No. 10, October 1973. 24 pp.
      - Item 2: High School Labor Studies: A Cooperative Effort for the Familiarization of High School Students With The World of Work, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
        21 pp. nd.
      - Item 3: A Tribute to Leonard Woodcock, 1977; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
        16-May-77.
      - Item 4: You and Your Membership in the UAW in Region 3, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
        19 pp. nd.
      - Item 5: You Can Help Build a Strong Local Union: The Future Is Up To You, 1974; Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
        July 1974. 31 pp.
      - Item 6: Your Union Dues: It Doesn't Cost to Belong to the UAW, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 29)
        15 pp. nd.
    - Mine Workers, United. We Make This Country Go. The United Mine Workers Bicentennial Calendar for 1976, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Musicians, American Federation of. Music is Your Business, Pamphlet (Box 4, Folder 31)
      9 pp. nd